

#### **Personal**

Name Hakan Karadeniz

**Address** Gaziosmanpaşa 34240 İstanbul

**Phone number** +90 531 392 1672

Email

hakan.karadeniz@outlook.com

**Gender** Male

**Driving licence** B

Website hakankaradeniz.github.io

**LinkedIn** linkedin.com/in/karadenizhakan

#### **Interests**

Playing Piano
Body Building
Playing Football
Bilgi Robotics Student Club

Languages

Turkish Native English B2

# Hakan Karadeniz

I completed my 4 years education year at the Department of Electrical and Electronics Engineering at Istanbul Bilgi University. I want to implement and manage national and international projects that touch people's lives in a company where I can use my experience, demonstrate my technical knowledge and skills, and be useful. In line with this goal, I continue to improve myself with the principle of life long learning.

#### **Education and Qualifications**

# **Electrical and Electronics Engineering**

Oct 2017 - Present

Istanbul Bilgi University, Istanbul

# **Business / Faculty of Open and Distance Education**

Oct 2020 - Present

Istanbul University

# Work experience

#### **Software Development Intern**

Apr 2022 - Jul 2022

Nettsi Informatics Technology, Istanbul, Turkey

- -Using command screen with Linux and mostly used commands.
- -Object Orianted Programming with C++, Standart Template Library, VSCode extensions.
- -I observed very clearly how important it is to work as a team and why the SCRUM is so important.
- -Basic knowledge about TCP/UDP protocols, OSI Layers, WireShark.
- -Using Git commands

## Working Student in University

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

Istanbul Bilgi University, Istanbul/Eyüpsultan

- -Teamwork and process management
- -Ability to speak and express oneself in public

#### **Electrical & Electronics Engineer Intern**

Sep 2020 - Oct 2020

YAMAS A.Ş., Bursa/Nlüfer

- -Project management
- -Team work

## **Skills**

# Linux ( Ubuntu ) C/C++ Python C# Java

#### Github

https://github.com/hakankaradeniz

#### References

Ümit Koç ( Mentor )

+90 538 433 75 37 umitkoc.com@gmail.com Nettsi Informatics Technology